Greg Lobrigo Jr.

Paranaque, Philippines | +63 945 321 7121 | greglobrigojr@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/greglobrigo/

GitHub: https://github.com/greglobrigo/

Web Portfolio: https://portfolio-greglobrigo.vercel.app/



October 2023 - December 2023

January 2023 - December 2023

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• **Proficient**: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, PHP, Laravel, Node, React, Nextjs, Serverless, Ruby on Rails, AWS Services, Pascal, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Scrum, Agile

EDUCATION

- Full Stack Web Development Avion School 2021
- BS Business Management Divine Word College of Legazpi 2016

WORK EXPERIENCE

The Grid Food Market | Role: Lead Developer

Technology: Reactjs, Nextjs, Nodejs, Pascal, Serverless, AWS, S3, PostgreSQL

Led the ETL for the sales consolidation of The Grid's 20+ stalls in Rockwell, Metro Manila

Contributions:

- Deployed an app that extracted sales data (receipts) from POS machines and uploaded them to the cloud
- Built a system that ran automated calculations on the receipts using SQL which turned to reports by end of day
- Built a web portal for the operations team that allowed them to download reports on demand as well as gain visibility on tenants able to upload their end of day sales reports
- Consulted with the Leadership team of The Grid regarding features and timelines

TMG (The Moment Group of Companies) | Role: Lead Developer

Technology: Exceljs, Nodejs, Nodemailer, Pascal, Serverless, AWS, S3, MySQL

Led the ETL for the sales consolidation of TMG's 50+ branches nationwide

Contributions:

- Deployed an app that extracted sales data (receipts) from POS machines and uploaded them to the cloud
- · Built a system that ran automated calculations on the receipts using SQL which turned to reports by end of day
- Automated the sending of several reports daily via email, including a report that provides monitoring of which branches were closed, or encountering issues with operations
- Provided them with a file browsing tool (S3 Browser) to view, download and manage their reports on demand
- Consulted with the Business Intelligence Team of TMG regarding features and timelines

SM SIA | Role: Fullstack Developer

March 2022 - December 2022

Technologies: Vuejs, Nuxtjs, PHP, Laravel, Lumen, PostgreSQL, MySQL,

Redis, Docker, Node, Serverless, AWS Services

SIA stands for Sales, Insights and Analytics. It is the software used by SM's accounting and operations team

Contributions:

- Focused on the core API which involves user management, roles, permissions, profiles and authentication, including the integration of AWS Cognito to the project
- Built several reports regarding the sales performance of their tenants
- Built an API called data-trends that plots a tenant's sales performance in a graph over a period of time

Freelance | Role: Fullstack Developer

October 2020 - February 2022

Technology: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Laravel, Ruby on Rails, MySQL, PostgreSQL

Worked on several individual projects that required small features built

- Contributed UI Changes that involves responsive design
- Built APIs that performed CRUD operations for storing user generated data

ABOUT ME

Hello! My name is Greg and I'm a web developer from the Philippines. Before getting into the tech industry, I worked in the BPO Industry for 3 years for several international companies and 1.5 years in a legal corporate office. Over the years I've developed my communication, leadership and collaboration skills

Programming and building systems is my passion, and I'm looking for new challenges and bigger roles to fill with my acquired experiences.